

SUMMARY

I am a Software Developer with expertise in the design, development, installation, testing and maintenance of software systems. As an engineer I am able to manage myself effectively during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team.

SKILL SET

Programing Language javascript, Typescript, Java, Go Basic

Front End

Nextjs, Vue, React, React Native (Expo), JQuery, HTML, CSS, Ionic, Tailwind, Motion.

Back End

Node Js, ExpressJs, Postgres SQL, MySQL, MongoDb, Redis, Apollo Server, GraphQL, Sequelize

Github:

https://github.com/albarmo

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/albar -moerhamsa-aa21681bb/

Albar Moerhamsa

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PORTOFOLIO

https://www.barworks.tech

WORKING EXPERIENCE

1000 STATRUP DIGITAL

Frontend developer | Feb 2021 - Mar 2021

Create mockup web design client and content management system, develop fontend for teskarir startup (user and content management system), integrate with gore API, implement the test algoritm.

FEEDLOOP

Software Engineer | April 2021 - 2023

Qore is a Low Code Platform, Develop client Qore base, integrate with API, implement the test, maintenance.

ENTRUST DIGITAL

Frontend developer - BRI SME LENDING | April 2023 - Now

Develop website base application for lending PT Bank Rakyat Indonesia

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

HACKTIV8

Fullstack Javascript Program | Jun 2020 - Nov 2020

learning about how to develop web application, how to work with server side and client side using javascript programing language

TRILOGI UNIVERSITY

Technical Information | Jan 2016 - 2021

CONTACT ME AT:

Email: moerhamsa@gmail.com Mobile: +62 812 8070 9980

Jalan H Mandor, West Cilandak, South Jakarta

Indonesia

PROJECTS

PORTOFOLIO

https://www.barworks.tech

PROJECTS

Sofdulur (2023)

Experimental and component sharing Nextjs, Nodejs, Postgres SQL link: https://softdulur-landing-git-mainalbarmo.vercel.app/

Plagams (2023)

plagams official store Nextjs, Nodejs, Postgres SQL link : https://www.plagams.store/

Magin Official Website (2022)

Kids clothes online shop Nextjs, Nodejs, Postgres SQL link : https://s-magin-app.vercel.app/

The Way (2022)

Mobile app life goal management IONIC, React. SCSS link: https://github.com/albarmo/theway

Terserahin (UI/UX) (2022)

link:

https://www.figma.com/file/zJDt3yvop9JcRNZhodidY0/Terserahin?type=design&node-id=103%3A52141&mode=design&t=LCZvuo8kbFbkySVn-1

Teskarir (2021)

psychological test website to determine career pathways

Qore, React, SCSS

link: https://teskarir.com